Guide to the Michael La Vean French documents collection, 1751-1851
George Mason University Libraries
- Michael La Vean French documents collection
  - Circular from the commissioner of the executive director of the Department of Morbihan in Vannes Re: order to find and arrest Alogny, Charles Franços, Marquis of Rochefort. 18cm by 22cm (Box 3, Folder 90)
    Circular ;18cm by 22cm
  - Letter No. 33. From Perrine le Mouet widow of Yves le Roy of Naizin to the administration of Morbihan. Re: Following the death of her husband and the theft of her horse, livestock, and other goods, she requests 10,377 livres. 1st Complementary day, year 4 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    Letter ;20.5cm by 32cm
    Signed by M. Letulzoff (for Mme the Roy of Naizin).
  - Circular No. 4; from Vannes from the Commissioner of Morbihan to the administration of Locminé Re: Request for more rigorous scrutiny of passports to prevent deported émigrés and priests from returning. 14.5cm by 20cm (Box 3, Folder 92)
    circular ;20cm by 30cm
    Signed: Faveroz
  - Circular no. 12 from Vannes from the Commissioner of Morbihan to the administration of Locminé Re: Renewed efforts to prevent émigrés from returning unpunished. 20 Brumaire, year [9 or 5] (Box 3, Folder 93)
    Circular ;19.5 cm by 30.5cm
  - Circular no. 19 from Vannes to the central administration of Locminé Re: Arrest warrant for Thomas Javarelle with his companion, Adelaide Picard 8 Frimaire, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    Circular ;14.5cm by 20cm
    Signed: Faveroy.
  - Circular No. 16; From Vannes to the administration of Locminé Re: passports. Emigrés and deported priests who have been returning to France because of non-enforcement of the laws. 9th of Frimaire, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    Circular ;17.5cm by 22.5cm
  - Circular from Commissary 9 Frimaire, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    Manuscript ;11 x 18.5 cm
    EMIGRES and deported priests Signed Faveroz
  - Circular No. 9; From Vannes to the administration of Lominé Re: Arrest warrant 22 Frimaire, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    Signed Faveroz.
  - Letter No. 5; From Pontivy to the Administration of Morbihan. Re: A reiteration of damage claims resulting from the chouans. 23rd Frimaire, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    Letter ;20.5cm by 32 cm
    Signed P. de Naizin.
  - Circular No. 22 [passports]; From the commissary of the executive director of Vannes to Loeminé Re: Reminder about the importance of the passport law of the 10 Vendémiaire. 8 Nivôse year 5 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Circular No. 200 8 Nivôse year 5 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    Circular ;18.5cm by 23cm
    Signed: Le Febries, Aubrey, Lauzer, Rou [hierfs]; Re: wearing the cocarde and disapproval of signs of loyalty to the old régime.
  - Letter No. [ ] From Vannes to the Commissary of the Executive Director of Morbihan. Re: abbé Remonin, Puissaye [sic]. Names of various enemies of the state whose counterfeit operations and other attacks must be resisted. 18 Nivôse year 5 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    Letter ;20cm by 30cm
    signed: Faveroz.
  - Circular No. 26; From Vannes to the central administration of Locminé Re: Warning that sedition is spreading and may not be long before manifesting itself. 18th Nivôse year 5 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    Circular ;14.5cm by 19.5cm
  - Circular from Vannes to the administration of Locminé Re: Grain supply to be requisitioned for troops stationed in the commune of Locminé 18th Nivôse, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    Circular ;11cm by 18cm
  - Circular No. 42; From Vannes to the Commissioner of Locminé Re: List of most wanted for arrest, Malerbe, Darbeville, Blanchet. 10th Ventôse year 5 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    Circular; 11.5cm by 18.5cm
  - Bulletin of laws of the Republic from 11 ventôse to 1 germinal, year 5 1 germinal, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    Circular ;12.5cm by 19.5cm
    signers:: Reubell; Lagarde; Merlin Minister of Justice
  - Letter from St. Brieuc to the administration of Loeminé Re: [Fran]ço is Frero, whose passport's validity is in question because it is without a stamp and because he's unemployed. 4 Germinal, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    letter ;21cm by 25cm
    Signed: Coreau, Perrary, Lorin, Prudhomme.
  - Official request No. 10 from the Administration of Locminé to Vannes for a police militia to pursue a murderer. 22 Germinal, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    Official request ;19 by 23.5cm
    Signed: Munihurey, Lauzen, le Febrez, M[ouneufs]
  - Circular No. 609 to Lominé Re: night patrols to guard against marauders and deserters. 3rd floréal, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    Signed: Laurey, Aubry, Lenne [Serine]. Mentions Jean Brevel [ery]
  - Circular no. 842; From the Central Administration of Morbihan in Vannes to the municipal administration of the canton of Lominé Re: Mandate for a written account of actions taken for a deserter whose passport has been confiscated. 15 prairial, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    circular ;11.5cm by 18cm
    Signed: Aubry, Lauzen and two others.
  - Letter from Blanchard pour le Precepteur de Lominé to Magistrates of Lominé Re: proposal to offer assistance to a destitute mother. 22 Prairial, year 5 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    circular ;19 x 23.5 cm
    signed Nuneburg
  - Passport 28 Vendémiaire, year 6 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    passport ;21 by 29cm
    Signed by local administrator, for Jean Joseph Bellou of Artigues.
  - Receipt for a debt owed by Loual[t] to Nonnes 29th Frimaire, year 6 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    Receipt ;13 by 9.5cm
    Re: 36 livres - paid 15 Nivôse year 10.
  - Bulletin of laws of the Republic Re: Reform of National Guard, Corrections to articles, etc. 26th Nivôse year 6 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    Bulletin ;13.5 by 21.5cm
    Signed: Bailleul, Oudot, Delpierre, Gomaire, Abolin; (Ratified). Council of Elders: Rousseau etc.
  - Circulaire 150. From Lominé Re: lease of a farm. 7 Pluviôse, year 6 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    circular ;18cm by 24cm
    Signed: Dubro[ife], Leladrum[z], [Munchure], Coursainty, Maino[z].
  - Public safety circular/letter No. 478. From Vannes to the administration of Lominé Re: Public safety circular/letter concerning thefts, guns, and enforcement. 2nd Germinal, year 6 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    circular ;11.5 by 18cm
    Signed: Lauzen, Lefebre, Aubm, 1 [eumelainé;]. [Pe] r [ovmuifs].
  - Circular No. 4707. From the commission of Nantes to the administrators of Lominé Re: Issuance of a passport to an inhabitant of Lominé. 2nd Prairial, year 6 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    Circular ;19.5cm by 25cm
    Signed: M. Petilot.
  - Official petition and decision. No. 87. From Locminé; Petition for an exception to the rule about straw roofs is Not granted. 13th Messidor, year 6 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    Petition ;17.5cm by 29cm
    Signed: A[rvouenc]
  - Abstract from the register of deliberations of the Central Administration of Morbihan. Re: Doing away with the communal hall to make way for a "Place" convenient to the market. 28 Messidor, year 6 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    Abstract ;21.5cm by 33.5cm
    Signed: A Lauzen.
  - Lease on farm and house in Vovigo Re: Terms of lease on farm and house and verge[r]s] in [Vo]vigo 22 Thermidor, year 6 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    Legal document ;19 cm by 24.5 cm
    signed Debroise, Le Padrun, Mouillart.
  - Record of a public meeting Re: foundation of a Talhoet-logieum in Moréac 22 Thermidor, year 6 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    Official record ;19 by 24 cm
    signed Le Padrun, Raoul le Roy, Debroise, Mouillart, Trevedy
  - Record of a public hearing at Locminé Re: land in town of Le Vigo: house, orchard, and 3 parcels land with 6 yr lease. 22 Thermidor, year 6 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    official record ;19.5 by 24 cm
    Signed Le Padrun
  - Letter from civil engineer to administration of Locminé Re: salary requirements for an expert engineering consultant 15th Fructidor, year 6 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    Letter; 15 by 19 cm
    signed Monnier
  - Record of an open meeting with citizens le Padreur, Raoul le Roy, Debroi[fs] and Mouillart with Toursaint, Commissaire; Re: Account of a public session of sale by auction of leasing rights to a farm in Mignon; signed Trev'[day] 13 Vendémiaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    Official record ;19.5 by 24 cm
  - Record of sale at auction 13 Vendémiaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    Sale at auction of a property with its land and chapel ;19.5 x 25 cm
    Public hearing Re: sale of property with its land and chapel. Conservation needed
  - Letter from Vannes to the municipal administration of Locminé 17 Vendémiaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    Letter ;17 x 22 cm
    A letter requesting a list of provisions signed Laumaillez, [R]opert, Lauzen, Re[owen], Petiot
  - Letter from Chafsin to administration of Loeminé Re: Ollivier la Cerre, farmer of Roscoet in Mauréac is in prison in Lominé on charges of stealing livestock; chouans may be the real culprits. 19 Vendémiaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    Letter ;15 x 19 cm
  - Circular from Vannes to the administration of Lominé Re: Law from fructidor mandating that a list of veterans' widows and orphans be made in order to provide compensation 25th vendémiaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    Circular ;17.5 x 22.5 cm
  - Circular from Vannes to towns Re: prohibiting purchase of English merchandise in order to strengthen French/Spanish relations. 26th vendémiaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    Circular ;18 x 23 cm
    Printed. signers:: Lauzer, Président, Ropert, Pétiot, Robert, and Laumailler
  - Copy of circular in Folder 128 Re: prohibiting purchase of English merchandise in order to strengthen French/Spanish relations. 26 vendémiaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    Printed.
  - Circular from Vannes to the communes re: law of the 17 Fructidor concerning ways of reforming the tax code. 29 Vendémiaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Notice No. 134 from Vannes to admin. of Lominé Re: Preparations and publicity for the fairs and markets in Morbihan including the publication of an almanac 30th vendémiaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    Official notice ;11.5 x 17.5
  - Letter No. 158 Re: list of owners of bureaus in Barnieres with sums paid annually 3rd Brumaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    Letter; 11.5 x 17.5 cm
  - Circular from Vannes to the central administration of Loeminé Re: payment order for Nicole, a farmer in C[auvain] in Na[izin] 3rd Brumaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    Circular ;11.5 x 18.5 cm
  - Circular Re: Increasing verifications of identification and arresting those without papers. Brumaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    Circular ;18.5 x 23
  - Letter from Vannes to Canton of Lominé Re: postponement of writing up charts of the draft to avoid misinterpretation. 26th Brumaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    Letter ;11 x 17.5 cm
  - Statement from jury of Pontivy to Lominé Re: arrest of Guillaume Menahye for harboring a refractory priest 11 Frimaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    Letter ;18 x 23 cm
  - Judgement of the criminal court of Morbihan Re: verdict of deportation for Pierre le Boucher, accused of harboring a refractory priest. 18th Frimaire, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    court record ;19 x 23 cm
  - Circular Vannes - Lominé regarding fire regulations in towns 3 nivôse, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    Circular ;11.5 x 17.4 cm
  - Letter from Vannes to the administration of Loeminé Re: getting information about a loan of 100,000 by a particular. 3 nivôse, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    letter ;11.5 x 17.5 cm
  - Circular Re: Provisional regulation of traffic on rivers, streams and canals and their jurisdictictions. 11th ventôse, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    Circular ;11.5 x 17.5
  - Letter from receveur and controler in office of guarantees in Vannes Re: gold and silver merchants 18 ventôse, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    Letter ;17.5 x 22
  - Letter from citizen Gayet to the administration of Lominé regarding bordereaux. 29 ventôse, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    Letter ;19 x 23.5
  - Copy letter from Minister of the Interior to Departmental administration regarding prison rations 26 pluviôse, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    26 pluviôse, year 7 ;18 x 28.5 cm
    Rations for prisoners in metric measurements in Lauzen, Chapeaux
  - Letter No. 774 from Vannes to canton of Lominé concerning rewarding soldiers for a brave act 2 Germinal, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    Letter ;11 x 17 cm
  - Circular Rennes-Lominé Re: request for background of Melanie [Pichon] and tailor residing in Lominé 1st Floréal, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    Circular; 19 x 23 cm
    etc
  - Public Notice from Vannes Re: government agricultural initiatives 11 floréal, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    public notice ;17 x 22 cm
    signed Lauze[n], President et al.
  - Address from the central administration in Vannes Re: Appeal to patriotism against the Royalists. 24 floréal, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    Speech ;18.5 x 23 cm
  - Circular from the Minister of War to local administration and commissioners of police and army Re: payment of national guardsmen., 8 Prairial, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    Circular ;21.5 x 33 cm; Printed signature: Milet-mureau
  - Circular No. 291 from Vannes to the Canton of Lominé Re: Postponement of writing up charts of the draft until further clarification, 17 Messidor, year 11 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    Circular; 11 x 17.5 cm
  - Legislation by the Council of 500 Re: List of charges of treason against the ex-directors 27th Messidor, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    Legislation ;12.5 x 20 cm
  - Circular No. 17 Re: Advice to the administration of Loeminé to respect the laws of August 22, 1791 by asking innkeepers to record each guest, even those only staying one night. 11 Thermidor, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    Circular ;15.5 x 18.5 cm
  - Letter from Vannes to the Municipal Administration of Lominé Re: Letter requesting a register 16 Thermidor, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Circular from Vannes to the administration of Loeminé and the commissioner concerning the surveillance of saltpeter and gunpowder. 17 Thermidor, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    Circular ;15 x 18 cm
  - Letter 93 from Vannes to the administration of Lominé Re: man arrested for not turning over his weapons will be released to be with his family until the trial. 24 Thermidor, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    Letter ;15.5 x 18.5
  - Letter No. 109 from Vannes to canton of Louminé Re: action will be taken to correct the injustice against the citizens of Louminé. 25 Thermidor, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    Letter ;15 x 18 cm
    Signed Rouen, Gauillard, Laumaillez et al.
  - Appeal from Vannes to the administration of Loeminé Re: vigilance against bearers of false passports. 5 fructidor, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    11.5 x 17.5 cm
  - Public Circular No. 1921 from Vannes to Locminé Re: Need for vigilance vis a vis those entering country with foreign or soldier papers 12th fructidor, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    Circular ;11 x 17.5 cm
  - Announcement Re: Requirement of a public posting at intersections 14 fructidor, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    public service announcement ;19.5 x 25 cm
    25 cent stamps
  - Report of a public meeting in Lominé Re: small farm in the village of Gocqu[es], Poe[...] and dependant plantings 22 Fructidor. year 7 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    official record ;19.5 x 24 cm
  - Letter from Vannes to Lominé asking an uncompensated baker to continue baking with assurance he will eventually be compensated. 2nd complementary day, year 7 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    Letter ;15.5 x 18.5 cm
  - Legislation by council of 500 Re: Extension of the delay accorded to juries deciding questions of military service. 12 vendémiaire, year 8 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    Legislation ;17 x 23.5 cm
  - Circular No. 97 Vannes to Lominé Re: Rules of provisioning to be more fair to detainees 19 Brumaire, year 8 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Legislation regarding salaries and organization of administrative districts. 22 Frimaire, year 8 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    Organization of administrative districts and salary amounts; printed; signers: Sieyes, Bonaparte, Roger-Ducos
  - Receipt for 12 francs received from Loualt owed by Louault's parents paid to Mac[on] 23 nivôse, year 8 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    Handwritten receipt ;13.5 x 18 cm
  - Receipt signed M.C. Louault for 72 livres cinq, which were brought to Citizen Boullée. 1 pluviôse, year 8 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    Receipt ;17.5 x 22 cm
  - Record of a public hearing Re: Cailloche, Lominé Re: 6 year lease on house and field at the port/bridge Cailloche in Loeminé 22 Thermidor, year 6 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    official record ;19 x 24.5
    (waterstains; watermark)
  - Notice of an auction 3 thermidor, year 8 (Box 8, Folder 166)
    Notice ;27 x 43 cm
    Wood and light service for the troops and military guards housed in the department
  - Circular Re: freedom of religion: government will no longer intervene in affairs of conscience. 19 Fructidor, year 8 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    Circular ;27 x 43 cm
    Printed circular
  - Copy of circular in Folder 167 19 Fructidor, year 8 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    circular ;27 x 43 cm
  - Circular from Vannes to Lominé Re: Interception of letters from émigrés; methods of establishing identitites of travelers. 20th Brumaire, year 9 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    Circular ;20 x 30.5 cm
    signed Faveroz
  - Letter from Brien[s] to Pontivy detailing robbery and murder of Mme. Briens, with request for reparations 179... (Box 4, Folder 170)
    Letter ;20.5 x 30 cm
  - Circular No. 22 Re: enforcing passport checks in response to repeated neglect of law. 8 nivôse, year 9 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    Circular ;11.5 x 18 cm
    Circular from [xavier]
  - Letter 35 from Executive Commissioner of Correctional Court of Pontivy to administration of Lominé requesting a table of all those under arrest in the administrative district. 1st Germinal, year 9 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    Letter ;17.5 x 22 cm
  - Avis au public Lominé Re: repairs to maison d'arrest. 25 floréal (Box 4, Folder 173)
    Public Notice ;19 x 24 cm
    hexagonal stamp
  - Notice of a hearing at Locminé Re: Repairs to the prison. 27 floréal (Box 4, Folder 174)
    Public Notice ;19.5 x 24 cm
    Round stamp; signed Toursaint (adjoint) et al.
  - Notice from the town hall of Locminé Re: land for sale at auction - Saint Jean Brevelary 27 Messidor, year 9 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    Official Notice ;19 x 20.5 cm
    round stamp; signed; needs conservation.
  - Avis au public 27 Messidor, year 9 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    Public notice ;19 x 24.5 cm
    Re: sale of lease for national properties in Mauréac hexagonal stamp
  - Official notice from the Mayor of Locminé Re: bidding on a property 7 Thermidor, year 9 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Record of a public meeting Re: Adjudication of an orchard and pasture near the clergy house. 16 Thermidor, year 9 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    public record ;16 Thermidor, year 9
    Needs restoration. water stains
  - Donation receipts for repairs of the church of Locminé from years 9-11 years 9-11 (Box 4, Folder 179)
    receipts ;various dimensions
    various signatures
  - Legal document describing the terms of a lease of a farm and farmhouse 23 pluviôse, year 10 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    legal document ;18.5 x 24 cm
    signed Le [P]adrun, Toursains and others
  - Letter from the Prefect of Morbihan in Vannes to the Mayor of Lominé Re: Pardon of Yves Even of Bignan for surveillance 30 pluviôse, year 10 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    Letter ;20 x 25 cm
    signed Jullien, Adjutant Commander
  - Beauties of England 1801 (Box 7)
    Book ;5 1/2 " by 8 1/4
    Illustration of counties of England v.1 - Bedfordshire, Berkshire, and Bucks
  - Notice of arrest of Louise le Bourdal of Lominé for non-compliance 26 vendémiaire, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    Official notice ;28.5 x 18 cm
  - Circular No. 191 from Sous-prefet of Pontivy to Mayor of Lominé Re: census of the commune 9 Brumaire, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    Circular ;11 x 17 cm
    signed D'haucou[z]
  - Letter No. 198 from sous-préfet of Pontivy to mayor of Lominé Requesting a chart of essential foodstuffs each trimester 19 Brumaire, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Letter No. 979 from Pontivy to Mayor and Deputy Mayor of Pontivy Re: Inquiring whether or not officers are ready to begin the draft. 4th Frimaire, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Letter from the sous-préfet of Pontivy to the mayor of Lominé two retirement pension stubs for Pierre and Guillaume requesting that their money be given to them. 10 Frimaire, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    Letter ;11 xx 17 cm
    signed D'Hauc[ouz]
  - Letter No. 930 Re: Inability to provide names of candidates for p[recep]teur in the commune. 21 Frimaire, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    Letter ;11.5 x 18 cm
  - Letter No. 96 from the sous-préfet of Pontivy to the Mayor of Loeminé Re: rent of a police building. 29 Frimaire, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    letter ;11 x 17 cm
  - Letter No. 276 from Pontivy to Locminé Re: Allocations for the repair of local byways. 11 Nivôse, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    letter ;15.5 x 19 cm
  - Letter No. 530 from the sous-préfet of Pontivy to Loeminé Re: sending a second copy of a table for the archives of the commune. 13 Nivôse, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Letter concerning education in Lominé Re: An invitation to nominate two candidates for a scholarship for students between 8 and 12 years old. 18 Nivôse, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    Letter ;15.5 x 19.5 cm
  - Letter No. 17 from the comptroller of contributions in Vannes to the Repartitioner of Lominé Re: Jean Sarantiére, who requests payments due her by law for a building she rents out. 25 Nivôse, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    Letter ;12 x 18 cm
  - Letter No. 1001 from Pontivy to Mayor of Lominé Re: Request for an account of budgeting expenses. 24 Ventôse, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    Letter; 11 x 17.5 cm
    signed D'Ha[ucouz]
  - Letter from the President of the criminal court, Morbihan, to Lominé Re: Condemnation of Lominé residents. 1 germinal, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    Letter ;20 by 25 cm
    Signed, Ferret
  - Letter from the sub-prefect of the arrondissement of Pontivy to Mayor of Lominé Re: request for copies of documents pertaining to road work. 1st Floréal, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Receipt for Blacker for money owed to Louault. 11 Floréal, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    receipt ;16.5 x 10.5 cm
    Receipt for 66 francs from Blacker for money owed Louault
  - Letter from the sub-prefect of the district of Pontivy to Mayor of Lominé Re: Letter regarding government approval. 17 Floréal, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    Letter ;12.5 x 20 cm
  - Receipt from a debt from the deceased Louault for 84 livres of which sum a part was paid by Ve Chereuin 20th Floréal, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    receipt ;15.5 x 19.5 cm
  - Letter from the sub-prefect of Pontivy to Mayor of Lominé Re: informing them of need for an advance payment to cover expenses for renovation of barracks 21 Floréal, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    Letter ;12 x 19.5
  - Letter from Pontivy to the Mayor of Lominé Re: Convocation of the electoral college of Lominé for a 3rd vote 23 Floréal, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    Letter ;16 by 10.5 cm
  - From Sub-Prefect D'Haucouz of Pontivy to Mayor of Lominé Re: request that the citizens of Lominé form a battalion of army reserves 1 Prairial, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    Letter ;11.5 x 19.5 cm
  - Notice from the Minister of the Interior to all concerned Re: Permission for hospices and "bureaux de bienfaisance" to erect thrones in churches, military courts and all publicly owned buildings 5 Prairial, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    Notice ;21.5 x 35 cm
    signed Mo[urieau]
  - Letter from the Sub-Prefect of Pontivy to Maire de Lominé Re: sending military pension for the trimester payable after the 1st of Messidor 6 Prairial, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    Letter ;12 x 19 cm
  - Letter from the Sub-Prefect of Pontivy to [Maire de Moreau] Re: sending military pension for the trimester payable after the 1st of Messidor 6 Prairial, year 11 (Box 5, Folder 204)